3219 Northridge Dr., Pueblo, CO 81008 ● 719-334-1494

Jace.armond.olan@gmail.com

Objective

To enter into a mutually beneficial employment opportunity that will increase my knowledge, skill sets and overall experience and at the same time add value to your business by being a productive team member, thought leader and contributor.

Work Experience

Albertsons

Cashier / Customer Service

August 2016 - Present

- Perform cashier duties, courtesy clerk duties and other miscellaneous assignments.
- Deliver an exceptional customer experience to all patrons.
- Continual work to improve processes and the customer experience.

Runyan Sports Complex

Umpire

March 2015 to August 2017

- Perform umpire duties for little league baseball games.
- Work with a diverse group of children and adults.
- Continually enhance conflict resolution and management skills.
- Provide guidance and mentorship as needed to newer members of the Runyan Field team.

Perfect World Music

Recording/Mixing Engineer and Drum Instructor

October 2018 - Present

- Perform audio editing and mixing for professional projects
- Work with a diverse group of clients in and out of the Covid 19 Pandemic
- Ability to work and perform under pressure, and in professional environments

Music Experience

Black Diamond Percussion

2018 - Present

Colorado State University Music Department

Student Council

2019

Pueblo Symphony & Orchestra

2018

Colorado State University Wind Ensemble

August 2017 – Present

Colorado State University Jazz Band

August 2018 - Present

Colorado State University Band – Drum

Captain

August 2018 - Present

Jace Olan

3219 Northridge Dr., Pueblo, CO 81008 ● 719-334-1494 Jace.armond.olan@gmail.com

Perfect World Music Studio/Academy

Centennial High School Band, Pueblo, CO August 2013 – May 2017

October 2018 - Present

Pueblo Municipal Band, Pueblo CO

March 2013, 2019 - present

Education

Colorado State University – Pueblo, Pueblo, CO

• Major: Mass Communications, Minor: Music Production

• GPA: 3.4

• Expected Graduation Date: December 2021

Centennial High School, Pueblo, CO

Skills

- Technology Savvy
- Strong written and verbal communications
- Excel in a Team and as Individual Contributor
- Experience with special needs children and adults
- 4 years experience working with ProTools
- Strong collaborative skills
- Ability to inspire others

References

Available upon request